I would like to talk to you today.
So again, can we talk about impressions?
Impressions?
Yes? Yes.
We used to work together in Akita,
We went on an expedition together,
We had dinner together twice.
That's when the time stopped,
I was always watching Tik Tok,
I was watching Tik Tok a lot, and I saw that he had dyed his hair,
I've been watching and following Tik Tok a lot.
It's embarrassing. Really?
I follow you and I highly recommend you.
Stop it!
It's really embarrassing.
I watch so much.
When I first started playing soccer, everyone was in elementary school or junior high.
I was in elementary school, right? When I first joined.
I had just entered the 6th grade.
It was really small, like a miniaturization.
It's not really small now.
I was really 12 or 13 years old,
I'm 18 years old now.
That's right.
I don't feel 18,
I don't even feel 18. I am 18 years old now!
I was surprised.
That's how I remember it.
That's how I feel.
You've grown up. You've grown up.
It was bad, wasn't it?
It was really bad.
But I couldn't understand what they were saying.
At that time.
I didn't establish a voice.
I don't know why.
I didn't know what to say either,
But I didn't know what they were saying.
I didn't know what all three of them were saying.
They were just making fun.
Yes, they are. They've grown up.
They've grown up. Yes!
So, the commonality is until March.
That's only three times, right?
I wondered if there was something to it, so I asked the other members earlier.
They said they have a lot of luggage on the expedition.
I see.
You have a lot of luggage, don't you?
Yes, a lot.
I have a lot too.
I see. We were together.
What do you take with you? For the expedition.
I don't bring anything extra.
I don't even pack my lotion in small packets, I just bring it all.
We were together. Peace treaty.
It stinks to be a member of the replacement team.
I think it's a waste of a drop of water for the replacement.
So that's how it is.
That's that part, That's the thing,
Replacement has to be used at home after all. It's a hassle, isn't it?
It's a hassle.
After that, I bring the clothes I'm buying.
Buy clothes? For when they get dirty?
I'm bringing a lot of socks.
Are you going to get them painted?
Are you planning to get your socks dirty?
In case they don't fit.
So, I'll also bring clothes for pictures,
And clothes for traveling,
You can take a bottle with you,
accessories.
I understand. I take it like an accessory.
I take a hair dryer.
Some hotels have hair dryers with low airflow.
I don't like that.
I see. Because I went to Okinawa,
What? Is it okay like this? Really?
Are you sure?
When I was in Okinawa, luggage on the plane usually weighed about 20 kilograms.
The limit was 19 kilos.
That's not safe. I went over the limit once.
What are you going to do? What do you do?
The staff said it was 40 kilometers before the limit, so I asked them to lift it with me,
I ended up weighing 23 or 25 kilos,
Clothes?
Clothes, souvenirs?
Souvenirs?
I told him that, and he bought a lot of souvenirs. I say that and I buy a lot of souvenirs.
We're the same.
I bought about 20,000 yen in Hokkaido the other day,
Too much.
One bill.
What's that? You're going to give it away? To your house.
It's all for your mom.
I like my mom.
I don't like your mother.
Wait a minute.
I don't like you.
That's a lie.
That's a lie,
I found a souvenir that your mother likes,
So, deliver it,
I'm doing it without buying my own.
That's amazing.
We have a lot in common.
Have you seen them since March?
I see. Because it was spring.
Did you see it because it was spring?
You saw it, right?
I don't know.
Not good at cleaning up?
I'm not good at cleaning up.
We're the same. Same.
Are the shadows dirty? Are the shadows dirty?
Very dirty.
It's the same.
It was the same.
Shadows are dirty.
I don't know why only my surroundings are scattered.
I want to be messy.
Aren't you the only one who is slow to clean up?
I'm slow.
You're also slow to get out.
I know.
I'm slow to get out of the car and stuff.
It's messy.
I don't make a mess of my car,
But there is.
There's bottled water in here.
There's also luggage in here.
I take off my shoes.
I know you take off your shoes.
I'm taking off my shoes.
I didn't take my shoes off.
That's where I was.
So, I'm sorry to move on.
There is a project that has become a regular feature of this nighttime conversation series between idols and idols,
That is the question from idol to idol.
We have prepared questions that we would like to ask each other,
I'd like to ask you some questions.
Let me start with the first one.
Lucky, I often hear this question from fans and members, Lucky often hears from fans and members,
Like he likes to do something for the group.
How can we help Mr. Tork sell more, to put it more simply?
Who told you that?
From a special person.
He's always thinking of something to do.
He's pretty funny and all that,
But then he's serious.
I've heard a lot about your ambitions for the future, Mr. Tork.
Ambitions?
In a lucky way.
What do you want to do in the future from Lucky's point of view?
Not just Lucky as a group, but Lucky himself, what he wants to do,
What kind of work do you want to do?
What?
Question.
I don't have any questions.
What? I don't know.
Really.
I don't know.
Because I want everyone to be in the spotlight,
I want everyone to be in the spotlight, so I'm thinking about how to stand out,
That's why, when I'm MCing or talking,
I want to create a world where no one loses anything,
So, I don't know.
We also do things like not speaking on purpose,
The ambition is for everyone to be different,
If I were to use a symbol, I would prefer a star instead of a circle,
I see.
Ambition is to have everyone sticking out, facing in different directions, but in the same shape.The ambition is that they all stick out, and are all going in different directions, but in the same form.
Lovely.
More.
Yay.
I like this about Lucky.
He says he's actually thinking a lot.
Maybe he's thinking a lot.
That's what I like about Lucky.
I love it.
That's right. That's one of the good things about Lucky. That's a good part, too.
But, people who know what they're talking about understand it.
I see.
Now I have conveyed one of Lucky's charms.
I did it. Thank you very much.
Acue.
I am such a serious person, I would like to ask you a question.
I'm afraid.
Shoe size.
You've got to be kidding me.
I'm serious.
So serious.
I'll have to tell my stylist.
When I see you again in the future.
I'll be in trouble.
Shoe size 23.5 to 4.
That's right. They're pretty big.
23.
3?
I guess we're alike.
They look like each other. They are similar.
Above.
Question from me.
That was all.
OK?
So, that's it.
I don't think there is anything wrong with it.
So, how was it?
It's been a while since I've seen you.
Is it okay to meet? Is it okay if I meet you?
It's been a while since we met.
It's been a long time,
I used to join when I was little,
I was a member of WishinLive when I was little, but I haven't done much recently,
I've only done a few shows with them, like Tamai de..,
It's true, isn't it?
It was true,
It's been a long time since we met,
It's been a long time since I've seen you, and you're really something,
Emo! It was emo.
That's the real deal.
It's really funny.
I felt like Lucky had grown up too.
It was fun talking to him.
It was fun.
I really want to see him again.
I want to do it together.
So, have you deepened your relationship with him?
Yes, we have deepened.It's deepening, isn't it?
You say rubber pins.
So,
I would like to end with that.
So far, we have met
Akane Takatani,
Inoue and Mr. Tagi,
Fune and Nimiyu.
Bye bye!
Wanderin' La!
Yay, yay, yay!
This story
Bye bye bye!